Guide to the Elaine Lobl Konigsburg Papers, 1967-1986 SC.1986.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Oversize Materials, 1967-1990; V.
  - Illustrations, 2.
    - Samuel Todd's Book of Great Inventions
      - Illustration for masks (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - Illustration for blankets (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - Illustration for french fries (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - Illustration for television (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Jennifer, Hecate, Macbeth, William McKinley, and Me, Elizabeth
      - Five Original Illustrations with Notes (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Journey to an 800 Number
      - Drafts of Dustjacket with Notes (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - The Second Mrs. Giaconda
      - Art for jacket (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Father's Arcane Daughter
      - Drafts of Illustrations (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Event Posters, 1987; 3.
    - Event posters for open house in celebration of addition of Konigsburg Papers to the SLIS, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Event poster for event at the Jacksonville Museum of Art (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Correspondence to Amy Kellman, 1967-1970; XVI.
  Scope and Contents
  This series includes correspondence by Konigsburg with Amy Kellman, a children's librarian and later the Coordinator of Chirldren's Services for the Carnegie Library of Pittsburgh. Correspondence consists of communications between friends and colleagues related to the early years of Konigsburg writing career.
  - Sept. 8, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Nov. 1, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Dec. 14, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Jan. 16, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - April 5, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Sept. 16, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Oct. 20, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Mar. 16, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Postcard, Aug. 3, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 9)